Guide to the Cartoon art collection, 1926-1988.
Cartoon art collection
- Series I. Cartoon Art, Prints, and Releases
  - Subseries It. Miscellaneous comics
    - It's Your Life by Richard Armstrong, 1974-1979 (Box 65, Folder 1-4)
    - Jimmy Connors column, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - John Keasler column, 1968-1974 (Box 59, Folder 3-13)
    - John Keasler column, 1975-1980 (Box 60, Folder 1-7)
    - Johnny Comet by Frank Frazetta (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Lema's Lesson by Champagne Tony Lema (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Love on Life by Philip H. Love, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Lowell Ponte column, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Merrie Chase by Mcevoy and Hubbell, releases, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - The Nebbs by Hess, releases, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Plain Jane by Frank Baginski, weekly releases, 1971-1974 (Box 57, Folder 1-4)
    - Pull up a Chair by Frank Markey, 1966-1967 (Box 60, Folder 10-11)
    - Pull up a Chair by Frank Markey, 1958-1960 (Box 61, Folder 6-7)
    - Robert Angus column, 1976-1977 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Robert Morrison column and resume, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Sakren comics releases, 1960-1962 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Stan Delplane's Postcard, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Sugar Blues by Gloria Swanson and Bill Dufty, 1977-1978 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Susan Mastro column, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Susie Q. Smith by the Walters, releases, 1954-1959 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Take My Word For It by Frank Colby, 1952-1953 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Tips for Teens by Elinor Williams, 1945-1946 (Box 62, Folder 18-19)
    - Tips for Teens by Elinor Williams, 1947, 1956-1967 (Box 63, Folder 1-11)
    - Walter Winchell column, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 8-9)
    - Way Out by Ken Muse, releases, 1968-1969 (Box 51, Folder 9-10)
    - Whitney Bolton column, 1964-1968 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Will Rogers column, 1926, 1932-1935 (Box 61, Folder 1-4)
- Series II. Political cartoons
  - Fischer, Ed (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Hesse, Don: Political cartoons, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Caricatures (Box 45, Folder 9-15)
  - Reg Manning, 1958-1960, 1965-66 (Box 51, Folder 12-15)
  - Reg Manning, 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 1-12)
  - Szep (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Warren, LD, 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
  - Wright (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Series III. Miscellaneous promotional materials
  - McNaught features packages, 1976-1981 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous promotional material, ca. 1982 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous promotional material (Box 56, Folder 16)
    Including Heathcliff, Condominium
  - Old Feature promos (Box 66, Folder 34-37)
- Series IV. McNaught Files
  - Ask the Teacher column, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Beauty after Forty, Edyth McLeod (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Bill Sakren, Blitz Brothers (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Boyle, Frank Debbie Debbie (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Bolton, Whitney daily column (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Barker, Eddie (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Boyd, L. Pass it On (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Buffles, Pat Thompson (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Butter and Boop (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Carroll, Nellie (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Creative Teacher (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Chief, by Joe Dawley (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Corcoran, Fred- Unplayable Lies (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Cuddles, Jack Wittry (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Dahl, Arlene (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Dixie Dugan (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Dixon Dugan (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Dreams, Steele Marion (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Dropouts, Howard Post (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Dunkel's Dilemma (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Felser, Larry (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Fisher, Ham- Estate (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Fisher, Ham (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Flagg, Dan (Box 65, Folder 28-29)
  - The Flintstones, Hanna-Barbera, 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - The Flintstones, Gene Hazelton, 1968-1971 (Box 65, Folder 31-32)
  - Gate, Alexander (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Hitchcock (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Horace and Buggy (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Hollywood Report, Jack Bradford, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Hope, Bob, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - The Jackson Twins, Dick Brooks (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - Jukebox, Linus Maurer (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - Karpin on Bridge (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - Kennedy Family (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Lain (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Lema, Tony (Box 65, Folder 43-44)
  - Lemmon, Leonore- A Twist of Lemmon (Box 65, Folder 45)
  - Lincoln Book (Box 65, Folder 46)
  - Love, Love on Life (Box 65, Folder 47)
  - McEvoy, Remy (Box 65, Folder 48)
  - McIntyre, O.O. (Box 65, Folder 49)
  - Material for book (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Manning, Reg (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Melody Lane, Jenny Capps (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Lain copy (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Mickey Finn (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Mr. Clubwoman, Gilmore (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Muddles (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Mutt and Jeff, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 8-9)
  - Norse by Norsewest (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Opinion Wise- Bill Sakren, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Ponte, Lowell, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Project X (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Pending (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Rogers, Will, 1969-1971 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Red Ryder correspondence (Box 66, Folder 16-17)
  - Rubright, memo pad (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Sez who? (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Stay Younger Longer (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Steincrohn (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Swayze, John Cameron, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Terry, Paul, 1954-1955 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Top view- Charlie Williamson (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Walters, 1954-1955 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Warren LD, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Wayout, Ken Muse (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Wenzel, Bill (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Wonderful Women (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Zeke Zekley (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Yogi (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - White House Memo (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Walter Winchell (Box 66, Folder 33)